http://www.kernowcraft.com/privacy-cookies

Contact
We're open! Orders are being dispatched as quickly as possible by our team, read more >
HomePrivacy & Cookies
Privacy & Cookies
We care about your privacy and will always keep your details secure.We have the utmost respect for our customers' privacy and look after your information with the same care and as we would want our information looked after. The team at Kernowcraft are customers too, of both Kernowcraft & other internet sites so we understand the importance of privacy and take the security of our customers seriously.
Privacy NoticeWe’ve tried to keep the information in our privacy notice simple and easy to understand. If you have any questions feel free to get in touch.
Cookies Like most websites, our website uses cookies. By using our site, you agree to our use of cookies. A cookie is a tiny file that helps remember something about you and using them helps to give you the best experience on our website. Cookies aren’t automatically good or bad, but without them, the website wouldn’t be able to remember you were logged in or remember what you were trying to buy, we also use them to help us improve the website by seeing how many people visit and which pages are popular. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers will automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. You can read more about cookies and how to disable them here. Please be aware if you disable all cookies that your user experience may be affected and you will not be able to shop on our website. If you want to delete cookies that are already on your computer, the ‘help’ section in your browser should provide you instructions on how to do this.
The video below explains in simple terms why cookies are useful and will help you understand why most websites use them.
Cookies we useFunctional cookies. These are essential for the operation of our website. They enable you to do things like browse the website, add a product to your shopping basket, sign in to your account and view your order history.Performance cookies. These are used to help us analyse how people use our website, for example counting how many people visit the website and to see how users move around our site. This helps us to improve how the website works.Personalisation cookies. These are used to recognise you when you return to our site. This enables us to personalise content for you, greet you by name and remember preferences and show you products you have recently viewed.Advertising cookies. These cookies are used to show adverts relevant to you, they also limit the number of times that you see an ad and help us measure the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns. You may occasionally see our adverts on websites like blogs and news sites.For a list of the cookies our website uses click here.
Who we areKernowcraft Rocks & Gems Ltd is the data controller of the personal information we hold about you. We are a data controller registered with Information Commissoner's Office. Kernowcraft Rocks & Gems Ltd is a company incorporated in England, our company number is 984779. Our registered address is Kernowcraft Rocks & Gems Ltd, Penwartha Road, Bolingey, Perranporth, Cornwall, UK, TR6 0DH. We use the information we hold about you, lawfully in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998 and the General Data Protection Regulation 2018 (GDPR).
EmailIf you subscribe to our VIP list you will receive email newsletters. You have the option to unsubscribe at any time, every marketing email contains a one-click unsubscribe link at the bottom of the email. To help us monitor and improve our e-newsletter and ensure we are sending you interesting features and offers, we gather statistics around email opening and clicks using industry-standard technologies.If you place an order with us you will receive order updates via email informing you about the progress of your order, these are part of our customer service emails and cannot be unsubscribed from. How to stop receiving marketing emails from usEvery email newsletter contains a one-click unsubscribe link at the bottom of the email, simply click this link and it will remove you from our email list. You can re-subscribe at any time via our website if you change your mind.
Postal Mail & CataloguesWe don't produce a regular paper catalogue anymore, however we may occasionally send offers, information on sales or mini catalogues through the post. If you would prefer not to receive any printed marketing through the post please email us at {~94|99|91|100|53|96|90|103|99|100|108|88|103|86|91|105|35|88|100|98~} to let us know and we will edit your customer account preferences.
Sharing your informationWe never sell your information or share it with company’s so they can email, call or mail you without your permission.We will occasionally share your information with trusted companies. For example, if you place an order with us we will pass your details to a courier so they can deliver your order, our payment processors so we can accept your payment and perform security checks to prevent fraud, IT companies who support our website and other business systems.We ensure that all companies we work with have a compliant privacy policy and they only have access to your data for the purposes needed to perform their specific services. Your privacy will be protected at all times.
Links to other websitesOccasionally we will link to other websites (for example where we feature photos of designers jewellery we will usually include a link to their website). This privacy notice only applies to our website so if you click a link to another website you should read their own privacy policies.
Any QuestionsIf you have any questions not answered here please contact our customer service team at {~94|99|91|100|53|96|90|103|99|100|108|88|103|86|91|105|35|88|100|98~} or on 01872 573888 they can assist with updating your information, advising how to unsubscribe from emails or deleting your account as well as any order or product queries you may have. If you wish to exercise your rights under GDPR regarding your personal information, please contact the Privacy Manager with details of your request to {~101|103|94|107|86|88|110|53|96|90|103|99|100|108|88|103|86|91|105|35|88|100|98~} or write to us at Privacy Manager, Kernowcraft Rocks & Gems Ltd, Penwartha Road, Bolingey, Perranporth, Cornwall, TR6 0DH.
Join our VIP list
Subscribe for free jewellery making advice, inspiration, new product updates & exclusive offers
We noticed you left some items in your basket on your last visit.Would you like to continue with this order?
Yes, continue from where I left off
No, empty my basket
